



goeller_b@yahoo.com



317-650-1129



Indianapolis, IN

TECH SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Google Apps for Education

INTERESTS



Carpentry



Music



Puzzles



Skateboarding

Bryan Goeller

Computer Science, Science, and Technology Teacher

Multi-talented problem-solver with 14 years of experience helping students find their talent for critical thinking. Curiosity and an abundance of energy create an educational experience for any young scientist or engineer that will inspire growth. Equipped with a positive track record of building relationships with students by placing trust and respect as the foundation of the learning community.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Computer Science Teacher 2019-present

Irvington Community Schools

2013 - Present

- Develop and implement a 6-8 grade CS Curriculum aligned to IN standards
- 4 years experience teaching with Code.org and CodeHS programs
- 5 years experience with Google Apps For Education
- 5 years experience providing Tier 1 Tech Support; 250 Chromebooks

6th Grade Science & Social Studies Teacher 2015-2019

- Develop and implement a STEM based Science Curriculum
- Develop and implement a Project-Based Social Studies Curriculum

2nd Grade Teacher 2014-2015

- Develop and implement a vertically aligned curriculum with grade level team
- Track and interpret test data (NWEA, F&P) to adjust and improve instruction

PE/Health Teacher Jan 2013-2014

- K-5 Physical Education and Health
- Plan and conduct Field Day events
- Leadership Committee

K-8 Wellness Teacher 2009-2012

Christel House Academy

2008 - December 2012

K-8 Physical Education and Health

Middle School Interventionist 2008-2009

Provide small group Math and Language Arts instruction (Title 1)

COURSES & TRAININGS

Front-End Engineer Course

codecademy.com

Introduction to Computer Science in JavaScript

codeHS.com

Indiana Gear Up - Math & Science College and Career Readiness June 2019

EDUCATION

BS Elementary Education

Indiana University Purdue University Indianapolis

Certification: Indiana Teaching License - Elementary Education: General Studies K-6

- Physical Education P-12

Graduation: May 2008